

□ (+44) 7488-769-169 | ■ peter789b@gmail.com | 希 Home Page | 回 GitHub | 面 tsun-to-gamedev

## Summary\_

Currently a Tool Programmer at Auroch Digital with 5 years of industry experience and expertise in Unity.

Contributed to the release of titles on a beloved IP for Apple Arcade in the past, and have released titles in both desktop and mobile platforms. My well-rounded skill set also includes commercial experience in developing enterprise applications. Comfortable working in an agile team with code review and continuous development.

# Work Experience\_

#### **Sumo Group - Auroch Digital**

Bristol, United Kingdom

TOOL PROGRAMMER

Oct. 2022 - Now

- In charge of an in-house data editor to overcome Unity's limitation on serialization. Improving code team's efficiency and supported designer's need on complicated data structure, with planned future UGC support.
- Cooperated with artists and extended Unity's timeline tool to create cinematic cutscenes for Mars Horizon 2.
- Building a code generation tool for UI programmers. Improving programmer's efficiency and catching bugs before they surface in the build.
- Created logging package to allow for better debugging in a complicated simulation game.
- Making core gameplay system for Mars Horizon 2, occasionally helping out in UI programming.

Q-Games Kyoto, Japan

GAME DEVELOPER

Nov. 2020 - Aug. 2022

- Cooperated with artists to create the main character in Frogger and the Rumbling Ruins, a well received title available on multiple platforms in Apple Arcade built with both Objective-C and Unity. Responsible for the player's scripting and majority of the UI.
- Helped maintain our in studio build machine with working experience in Jenkins and Mercurial SCM.
- · Assisted in the release of a major update for Frogger in ToyTown, from introducing new features to bug fixing.

#### **InCrowd Sports**

Brighton, United Kingdom

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Jun. 2018 - Sept 2019

- Involved in development and maintenance for 18 different Android apps using Kotlin. Significant work including working with third party for authentication of premiere videos.
- Creating demo plugins with WPF and Unity for an industry leading LED display software built in C#.
- Worked with Bitbucket Pipeline and Docker in the process of improving the build pipeline.

### Tech Demo\_

#### **Procedural Tree Generation**

MESH MANIPULATION, PROCEDURAL GENERATION

• Porting a tree generation algorithm invented by Nicholas McDonald to Unity. This is an experimental project to explore the possibilities of generating trees dynamically.

#### **Tower Defense**

AI, PROTOTYPING

• A prototype project attempting to use reinforcement learning in game development. Enemies pathfinding AI is driven by reinforcement learning and animation is entirely procedural

## Education

## **University of Sussex**

United Kingdom

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

• First honour graduate with award winning performance, worked as a lab assistant in the University to help teaching.